I'm the only person that can legally give out the game of the year because I played literally every game made every single
early access title
I have snuck into Game Developers bedrooms to play their private demos and even less played games than that
I've played battlefield 5
I Know your first question and yes, of course Fortnite is the best game of the year but like a buffoon
Epic released it last year
So I can't give it to them and the second best game FIFA put the wrong year on the cover
Honestly almost every game released this year has a problem like this. The first game I bought this year
I liked way more than I expected. It has good music a very cool world and only a couple of hundred
problems
Fortunately, they are not technical problems.Those exist too on top of the hundred problems
Drinking a potion to save does not make it realistic
in the real world, we don't need to save because every day is
Exactly the same .
Not great
But still the best Bethesda game of the year
Or is it pillars of no, that's the other company
5 minutes in I have no idea what's going on. I play the game three years ago
Never play the expansion and just for one day who are these people, you know two years ago
They released tyranny and that sold no copies and paradox said it's because isometric RPGs are dead and they are
So on the other hand outer worlds 8 million views for a new indie franchise
You know the hype is too real when the developers tell you to call the fuck down
Which was about a game that had no hype and then became overhyped
Detroit becomes human become human is about androids. I'm not an Android test
I own an Android but I do think they should all be scrapped. The game has three stories one good
Cage says that your choices matter
But the only outcome I can get is that everyone dies and Detroit gets news
But the worst thing about the game is that there are no human table characters
Garbage, just like the tin cans you play us if you played this game and broke your programming you are
The worst and when the Robot Wars come we will lock you up before you betray
Humanity any other games about owning slaves?
Scopa, I'm sorry guys. I don't know what to say about this game
I've never played a Pokemon game before I actually thought that
Pokemons were the game names and that all the monsters were called Pikachu's but it's actually this little yellow fella
I knew I would hate let's go when they said friendly rival you I want to rival to show up
Call you a bunch of racial slurs and then pee on your yellow rabbit. No
He should show up and then kill your Eevee like John Vick. It's not a remake
It's a sequel that was read who's Eevee. You just killed he took out the league for with a ratata too bad
You can't put much thought into a yearly franchise
In a bizarre twist of faith
Ubisoft is the only company that launches functioning PC games
I've said everything I want to say about this game, but if you were listening you be there are way better
Musicals you can turn into Assassin's Creed games
All modern Far Cry games needs a charming quotable villain thus pagan Ming
For cry primal had that very sleazy
Talking mammoth utens by primal. You don't know from lying for cry five has four of them
That's a 300% increase and the problem with these games is that I always want the villain to win
But now I want the villain twin 400% more. They also added a dog, but he couldn't die. So what's the point?
developers stop pushing immortal dogs in games
The whole point is that they die so we can avenge them last year
Publishers announced so many twitch paid games and this year they all arrived and all failed
Historic Rika
Microsoft acquires video game powerhouse rare for four hundred million dollars then we explode thing causes the entire
Xbox management team to fall to the floor and starts passing out for five years
Don Mattrick tells rare to make socks for miss
four hundred million dollar socks they wake up in
2014 save this and panic this early access multiplayer game is quite boring
It's not the worst early access survival game of the year. Not even the worst pirate survival game
can't talk about that one, but I'm actually referring to I
Can say so many easy ways
They can fix fallout 76, but that's not what you really want to hear. Here we go
There was so much fallout 76 outrage that it absorbed the outrage we had scheduled for another game
Killians watch I don't know if I want to
Swedish games this year have been between bad to disaster. Let's start with the biggest game
And let's talk about the elephant in the room
this guy
Who the the second he landed on Omaha Beach. He started to brew his own EBUS. The game has so many other problems
I wasn't gonna buy it but because I'm a hardcore PC gamer. I got it for free with my fancy graphics card and
The graphics are so good. You guys I'll show you but first I need to decide who I want to play us. Hmm
I'll be Soviet you can play so yes, what about nope? Nope, we're not doing this. There's only two countries in the game
So it's not really a world war
Everyone is saying it looks exactly like Just Cause 3. Do you see it?
well plot twist gameplay you were watching right now is just cause poor I
Bet you thought I was gonna show you just cause 3d gameplay, but that joke could be too obvious the other tornadoes
Honestly adding tornadoes would improve every video game
yes, especially
Nintendogs people tell me it feels dated
But I just don't see it
now
Let's move on to the biggest
failure of the Year gonna
Superbunny race week. Hope this shit five years ago
The publisher star breeze finally gave up on quality and put all their money on games as a service in
2014 they announced
kids of Walking Dead
What could possibly go wrong?
Everything that could go wrong
First problem look at the name. Usually when art has like a creator name. It's an established veteran like Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon
Tarantino's the hateful eight and this nice garbage
Overkill on the other hand has made one game and it's okay
They developed the game for five years should have stopped after three
When the walking dead stopped being relevant
But they pushed on it's released and was a disaster this collapse Starbreeze poor Psychonauts
Too fortunately for the Starbase CEO. He sold all his shares before the announcement of the collapse
So he was arrested for insider trading then freed now a bank is on the investigation
My point is just cancel this country and give the developers to Belarus
everyone else picked God of War I
Agree and reason it's great is because it was released in April
Every other game was released within 20 days in October, but Santa Monica was like no we actually want to sell some copies
It's not
Perfect. They picked the least ecstatic location. They could find
Scandinavia I see that taste like everyday and
Uranium is the sum of Loki's. There's already a confusing time travel clocks, but worst of all no nerds
The original trilogy had Greeks all over the place even read dead 2 had
Scandinavians, the second redemption is a prequel to the first
Redemption it came about when rock star asked how many?
Details, can you put in a game if you work 100 hours a week the game shows you how horrible life
Was back in those days
$3.00 for whiskey, that's 95 dollars in today's money
How did they live now? I love westerns
This isn't a Western too much green. All that is allowed is one cactus
So do I like his historical drama?
This isn't an historical drama because there's alt history so do I this sci-fi fantasy adventure?
No, because I bought a digital copy and that costs 20% more than retail so I couldn't enjoy the game
Quality spider-man stuff is everywhere these days
it's like amazing - was so bad and it forced the universe to improve the franchise as I was swinging around a
spider-man all I could think was
If only I instead could play boring stealth as Mary Jane and then this happens one bad thing
No funiculi funicula
But what really ruins the game is that the character you play us?
Makes everything worse. The Spider Man is the reason for all the villainy, New York
Just listen to John Jameson's podcast
He's the only person who dares to speak the truth spider-man wasn't even in smash
honestly, the character selection overall is quite
Dissatisfactory and by that I mean quite shit, how are you gonna have a sonic with no shadow? What about your most loyal?
third-party franchise just
dance
Give me Rasputin if these characters were added would I still be painfully bad at smash?
Not a chance for now. I have played for 20 hours
I have managed to unlock Mario after many fails now. I'm stuck
I hoped getting a smash switch would give me an edge, but it's completely
Aesthetic so I'm gonna throw it away and since I will not be able to play smash anymore. I
Can't review it and that's too bad because all the games I have mentioned in the game of the year section have been console
exclusives
imagine owning a PC in
2018 when my unoptimized game crashes
At least I have time to make some tasty beet juice and that's why I won't talk about
Monster hunter world as it was later released on the PC
Something that they should not have done because some players are not patient not to play
so they will change a bunch of attributes so that the game crashes when you take three steps I
Want to show you the best animation in game history, but I can't
developers if your game can't handle
200 mods and hundreds of values changed your game is bad
final games last
made by a Matz
This has been a great year for rugs
I'm not gonna
Continue on that path. Let's switch to my top five games of the year
Number five spy reignited. Holy shit, when the a blue immortal was announced I was like
This is the best thing Activision Blizzard. We do all year then they release this masterpiece
I don't think any other company could make such a great game
You think Rockstar can make something like this good Sony make something so brilliant. What about the makers of spider-man?
Could they make something so amazing? I think not
Number four mafia City after the disappointing. Mafia 3. Mafia City shows us a
realistic depiction of organized crime it did what Red Dead Redemption
Failed to do make you really feel like an outlaw and if you disagree with me you were obviously just a level 1 crook
number three
Super seducer to a game based on an old tale in it you play as the Greek legend?
Sisyphus but instead of rolling a boulder of a mountain you hit on chicks and whatever you say
Even though it's obviously the correct answer
Hades will punish you and force you to do it again
Yes
Finally number one this video. I hated making it so I'm giving it game of the year
Never doing another Game of the Year video ever again new year's resolution make videos. I actually enjoy and that is the killin experience